Guide to the Shael Shapiro Papers MSS.200
Fales Library and Special Collections
Shael Shapiro Papers
1954-2006
Fales Library and Special Collections
Shapiro, Shael
MSS.200
75 Linear Feet in 39 manuscript boxes, 5 oversized flat boxes, and 396 flat file folders.
3.08 Megabytes in 58 computer files.
Shael Shapiro is an architect who was instrumental in the writing and passage of the so-called "Loft Law" that in 1971 allowed artists to legally live in downtown Manhattan lofts. The Shael Shapiro Papers date from 1954 to 2006 and contain architectural drawings and reproductions of numerous buildings throughout New York City and records documenting Shapiro's SoHo based architectural practice from the 1970s to the early 2000s. The bulk of the records are paper with some born-digital files.
Scope and Content Note
The Shael Shapiro Papers date from 1954 to 2006 and consist of architectural drawings and reproductions, correspondence, building specifications, photographs (primarily building exteriors and interior details), inspection reports, architect's and engineer's reports, financial and legal documents related to Shapiro's architectural practice on Wooster Street in the SoHo neighborhood of Manhattan, N.Y. from the 1970s to the early 2000s. The architectural drawings and reproductions found in the collection include floor plans, elevations, details, structural, plumbing and mechanical drawings, and some sketches. Most reproductions are diazotypes or ink on plastic, and most original drawings are graphite and/or ink on paper or on plastic. Some architectural drawings and reproductions were produced by consulting engineering firms, most often by WYS Design Partnership, Consulting Engineers. The collection also contains New York City Department of Building applications, permits and certificates, documents and correspondence with the City of New York Landmarks Preservation Commission, as well as correspondence and registrations with the New York City Loft Board. Although Shapiro's most notable work is the conversion of lofts in downtown Manhattan, the collection contains material related to projects (identified by job number and address, building, or client name) throughout New York City, with a small number of projects located outside of New York.
Four architectural projects in this collection contain electronic records, which include correspondence and renderings.
Biographical Note
Shael Shapiro is an architect whose practice was largely based in the SoHo neighborhood of Manhattan, N.Y. He studied architecture at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, in Troy, N.Y., and moved to SoHo in 1967, living in one of the artist George Macuinas's Flux Houses on Wooster Street. Shapiro worked on architectural projects throughout New York City, but his most significant work was focused on artists' lofts in downtown Manhattan. Shapiro was instrumental in the writing and passage of the so-called "Loft Law," enacted in 1971, which allowed artists to legally live in lofts downtown, and helped shape the growing community of artists in 1970s SoHo.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Shael Shapiro in 2007. The accession number associated with this gift is 2007.200.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by street name, then numerically by building number, with avenues first (numerical, then named), followed by numbered streets (proceeding East to West), named streets, then project names without addresses. Because of the varying sizes of drawings in the collection, a project may be split among multiple different containers, including boxes and flat file folders.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Architectural drawings can be accessed as exported as .svg files through Adobe Illustrator. Software to view .dwg files from the collection, which are presumed to be created by computer-aided design software, is not avaialble as of 2024. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Architecture -- New York (State) -- New York.; Architectural drawings (visual works); Architectural records.; Artists and community -- New York (N.Y); SoHo (New York, N.Y.); Artists -- Dwellings -- New York (State) -- New York.; Architecture, Modern -- 20th century.; Lofts -- Law and legislation -- New York (State) -- New York.; New York (N.Y.). Landmarks Preservation Commission; New York (N.Y.). Department of Buildings
- Architectural Records
  - Job: 7118, 919 Third Avenue, LIU Urban Design Association, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 11, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 8639, 983 Third Avenue, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 7908, 54 Fifth Avenue, 1987 (Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 7908, 74 Fifth Avenue, 1979-1981; cuid40889 (Box 34, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 16, Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Job: 8004, 74 Fifth Avenue, Rauch Loft, 1980; cuid40874 (Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 8202, 95 Fifth Avenue, 1982-1990 (Box 18, Folder 2, Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Job: 7913, 105 Fifth Avenue, 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 8929, 111 Fifth Avenue, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 3-4, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 7911, 118-120 Fifth Avenue, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Job: 7845, 142 Fifth Avenue, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Job: 7863, 208 Fifth Avenue, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 7005 / 7005 A / 7112 / 7409, 200 Sixth Avenue, 1971-1974; cuid39151 (Box 30, Folder 12, Flat-file-folder 5R, Box Shared Fales 097, Folder 14)
  - Job: 7935, 450 Sixth Avenue, 1980; cuid40876 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Job: 8844, 1221 Sixth Avenue, Kellwood Co., 1988 (Box 20, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Job: 8919, 501-507 Eighth Avenue, 1984-1990 (Box 18, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 0211, 116 Tenth Avenue, Susan's Gallery, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1, Box 39)
  - Job: 7724, 1160 Park Avenue, Blumberg Bedroom, 1977; cuid39146 (Box 28, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 7, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Job: 9819, 99 Park Avenue South, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 7215, 325 West End Avenue, Hecht Apartment, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 14, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 7642, 62 East 1st Street, 1975-1977 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Job: 7433, 89 West 3rd Street, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Job: 7708, 28 East 4th Street, 1982 (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 8113, 28 East 4th Street, 1982-1987; cuid39231 (Box 11, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 10, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 7922 / 9242, 29 East 10th Street, 1979-1981 (Box 37, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 17, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - 303 West 10th Street, 1996-1997; FA_MSS_200_ER_3
  - Job: 7410, 54 East 11th Street, Gene Eagles Loft, 1974; cuid40877 (Box 8, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 7806, 14 West 11th Street, 1978-1979; cuid39106 (Box 31, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 17, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 9711, 359 West 11th Street, 1987-1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Job: 7765, 373 West 11th Street, 1977 (Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 8904 / 7912, 24 West 12th Street, 1977-1989 (Box 19, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Job: 7909, 380 West 12th Street, 1979-1981; cuid39107 (Box 34, Folder 2-3, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 10, Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 9020, 383 West 12th Street, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Job: 7217, 8 West 13th Street, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Job: 7119, 30-34 West 13th Street, 1972-1978; cuid39102 (Box 29, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 15-R, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 7613, 30-34 West 13th Street, 1972-1978 (Box 16, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Job: 7435, 43 West 13th Street, 1975-1984 (Box 14, Folder 2, Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Job: 7839, 43 West 13th Street, Dignan's Loft, 1978-1979; cuid40886 (Box 23, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 15, Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Job: 7505, 129 East 15th Street, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 13, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 7421, 42 West 15th Street, 1974-1978; cuid39134 (Box 8, Folder 5, Box 39, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 7781, 58 West 15th Street, 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 7782, 60 West 15th Street, 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 12, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 7923, 153-159 West 15th Street, 1979-1981 (Box 37, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 7815, 15-17 East 16th Street, 1978-1979 (Box 35, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 7512, 55 West 16th Street, undated; cuid39132 (Flat-file-folder 11R, Flat-file-folder 3R)
  - Job: 7727, 14 West 17th Street, 1979; cuid39101 (Box 28, Folder 6, Box 40, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 13, Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Job: 7726, 141-145 West 17th Street, 1977-1979; cuid41092 (Box 28, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 8203, 15 West 18th Street, 1982-1993 (Box 18, Folder 1, Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Job: 7734, 139-149 West 19th Street, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 20-R)
  - Job: 9816, 220 West 19th Street, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Job: 7917, 20 East 20th Street, 1979-1990 (Box 26, Folder 7-8, Box 31, Folder 11, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 4, Box 41, Folder 24, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Job: 9124, 20 East 20th Street, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Job: 7742, 6-8 West 20th Street, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 18-R)
  - Job: 7929, 120 West 20th Street, 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 7704, 143 West 20th Street, Koffsky Loft, 1977; cuid39084 (Box 27, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 7725, 143 West 20th Street, 1977-1980; cuid39147 (Box 28, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 16, Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Job: 7809, 29 East 22nd Street, 1978-1981; cuid39155 (Box 35, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 11, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 8015, 205 East 22nd Street, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 4-5, Box 14, Folder 1, Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Job: 7927, 129 West 22nd Street, 1976-1987 (Box 36, Folder 1-2, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 9006, 135 West 22nd Street, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 7735, 147 West 22nd Street, 1978-1992 (Box 29, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 9, Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Job: 7811, 148 West 23rd Street, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Job: 7937, 148-156 West 23rd Street, 1978-1980 (Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 7712, 149 West 24th Street, 1977-1985 (Box 27, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Job: 7750, 109 West 26th Street, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Job: 7711, 154-156 West 27th Street, 1970-1978 (Box 27, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 3-L)
  - Job: 7903, 151 West 28th Street, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 3-5, Box Shared Fales 109, Folder 8)
  - Job: 7721, 34 East 30th Street, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Job: 7733, 22 West 30th Street, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Job: 7774, 31 West 31st Street, 1977-1979 (Box 24, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 7736, 34 West 31st Street / 1232-1238 Broadway, 1977; cuid39157 (Box 29, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 9508, 114 East 32nd Street, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 16)
  - Job: 9428, 14 East 33rd Street, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 7747, 527 West 34th Street, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Job: 7838, 114 East 36th Street, 1977-1981; cuid40885 (Box 22, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 13, Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Job: 7829 / 7865, 361 West 36th Street, 1978-1983; cuid39110 (Box 37, Folder 8, Box 39, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 12, Box 31, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 11, Box Shared Fales 109, Folder 11)
  - 267 West 43rd Street, Dr. Schreiber's Office, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 9250, 552 West 43rd Street, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Job: 7771, 10 East 44th Street, 1954, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 7205, 539 West 45th Street, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Job: 8723, 42 West 48th Street, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 7713, 308 East 49th Street, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 12, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Job: 9531, 630 West 52nd Street, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5, Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Job: 9918, 254 West 54th Street, Studio 54, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 2-3, Box 41, Folder 1-2, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 7110, 205 West 57th Street, Messing Residence, 1972; cuid39152 (Box 30, Folder 13, Box 40, Folder 7, Box Shared Fales 097, Folder 18)
  - Job: 7615, 320 West 57th Street, undated; cuid40875 (Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Job: 8649, 518-556 West 57th Street aka 503-561 West 56th Street, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Job: 8813, 140 West 58th Street, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 5, Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Job: 9309, 150 East 61st Street, 1978-1994 (Box 13, Folder 3, Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Job: 7848, 128 East 65th Street, 1978-1980; cuid40891 (Box 36, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 9244, 49 East 67th Street, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Job: 7925, 27 West 67th Street / Miscellaneous Projects, 1979-1986 (Box 37, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 4 Left)
  - Job: 7847, 45 East 68th Street, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 7821, 45 East 68th Street, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 7915, 412 East 73rd Street, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Job: 7826, 40 East 74th Street, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Job: 7413, 4 East 77th Street, 1965-1974 (Box 12, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 9005, 519 East 82nd Street, 1984-1990 (Box 18, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Job: 8714, 316-320 East 86th Street, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 7830, 32 West 86th Street, undated (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Job: 7125, 230 East 97th Street, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 2, Box Shared Fales 097, Folder 15)
  - Job: 9003, 239 & 247-253 West 116th Street, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1-4, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 7221, 637-649 West 125th Street, Reality House Inc., 1972 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Job: 0007, 21 Astor Place, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 7810, 10 Beach Street, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 7751, 48 Beach Street, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Job: 9036 B, 48 Beach Street, 1990-1994 (Flat-file-folder 22)
  - Job: 7405, 10 Bleecker Street, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Job: 7867, 33 Bleecker Street, 1979-1981; cuid39080 (Box 41, Folder 11, Flat-file-folder 11, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 7816 / 8634, 54 Bleecker Street, 1978-1985; cuid39105 (Box 35, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 7, Flat-file-folder 10, Box 11, Folder 4, Box 41, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 8, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Job: 7801, 289 Bleecker Street, 1978; cuid39156 (Box 32, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Job: 7001, 21 Bond Street, William Israel's Farm Artists' Coop, 1970-1972; cuid39103 (Box 30, Folder 7, Box 40, Folder 15, Flat-file-folder 4R, Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Job: 7858, 21 Bond Street, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 0020, 50 Bond Street, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Job: 7803, 74 Broad Street / Job 7805, 9-11 Maiden Lane, undated (Box 31, Folder 10, Box 32, Folder 8)
    Related Materials
    See also: 9-13 Maiden Lane.
  - Job: 8654, 361 Broadway, 1984-1991 (Box 19, Folder 2-3, Box 20, Folder 1-3, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 13, Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Job: 7833, 366 Broadway, 1978-1980; cuid39094 (Flat-file-folder 1, Box 31, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 9133, 398 Broadway, 1991 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Job: 9126, 401 Broadway, circa 1995 - 1996 (Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 7446, 431 Broadway, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Job: 9808, 433 Broadway, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 8302, 480-482 Broadway, 1983-1984; cuid39227 (Box 1, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Job: 7635, 482 Broadway, 1977-1981; cuid39141 (Box 17, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 12, Flat-file-folder 16)
  - Job: 7926, 491 Broadway, 1982-1989; cuid39109 (Box 37, Folder 1-2, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 4, Box Shared Fales 109, Folder 7)
  - Job: 9713, 506 Broadway, 1997 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Job: 7412, 510 Broadway, 1969-1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Job: 0220, 510 Broadway, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 8229, 515 Broadway, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 18, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 9229, 524 Broadway, 1994-1997 (Box 14, Folder 3-4, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 15)
  - Job: 8227, 537 Broadway, 1983-1995; cuid41090 (Box 5, Folder 6-7, Box 6, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 15, Flat-file-folder 7)
    Scope and Contents
    Also contains drawings of an adjacent building, 110 Mercer Street.
  - Job: 7763, 542 Broadway, Caryatids of Broadway, 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 18, Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Job: 7868, 543 Broadway, 1978-1993 (Box 32, Folder 13-14, Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 8923, 543 Broadway, Rockwell Loft, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 6R)
  - Job: 9206, 545 Broadway, 1992 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Job: 9026, 561 Broadway, The Singer Building, 1979-1996 (Box 21, Folder 5-6, Box 22, Folder 1-2, Flat-file-folder 2, Box 39, Folder 15-16, Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 10, Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 8841, 670 Broadway, 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 5, Box 22, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 10, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 8019, 704 Broadway, 1980-1982; cuid40882 (Box 12, Folder 6, Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Job: 8816, 704 Broadway, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 7814, 714 Broadway, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 7846, 716 Broadway, 1978-1981 (Box 16, Folder 9, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 8707, 860 Broadway, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 7832, 1200 Broadway, 1977-1980 (Box 31, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 8, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 7916, 1200 Broadway, Stern Loft, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 17, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Job: 7731, 1225 Broadway, 1976-1979 (Box 29, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Job: 7762, 2061-2065 Broadway, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 13, 19, Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 11, Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Job: 7113, 330 Broome Street, 1972-1973; cuid40887 (Box 29, Folder 12, Flat-file-folder 12R, Flat-file-folder 2-l)
  - Job: 7632, 423 Broome Street, 1977-1984; cuid39140 (Box 17, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Job: 9400, 426-428 Broome Street / 38 North Moore Street, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 2, Box 39, Folder 12)
    See also: 38-40 North Moore Street.
  - Job: 7778, 445-451 Broome Street, 1980-1992 (Box 32, Folder 1-2, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 6)
  - Job: 7767, 447 Broome Street, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Job: 7737, 457 Broome Street, 1970-1979; cuid41093 (Box 29, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 7629, 460 Broome Street, 1978; cuid40884 (Box 17, Folder 4, Flat-file-folder 7, Flat-file-folder 15)
  - Job: 7910, 462-464 Broome Street, undated (Box 26, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - 472-474 Broome Street, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Job: 7510, 476 Broome Street, 1975; cuid39138 (Box 15, Folder 11, Flat-file-folder 2R)
  - Job: 7723, 477 Broome Street, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Job: 7518, 480 Broome Street, undated (Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 9034, 482 Broome Street, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 7-8, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 7009, 485 Broome Street, Soho Stake, 1970-1973; cuid39149 (Box 30, Folder 10, Flat-file-folder 4R, Flat-file-folder 16-R)
  - Job: 7312, 485 Broome Street, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Job: 7853, 485 Broome Street, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - 86-31 Dongan Avenue, Elmhurst, NY, 1971 (Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 7204, 118 Forsyth Street, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Job: 7618, 54 Franklin Street, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 9908, 139-141 Franklin Street, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10, Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Job: 7625, 158 Franklin Street, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Job: 7319, 1 Gramercy Park, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Job: 7745, 1 Gramercy Park West, 1974-1978 (Box 25, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 7444, 64-70 Grand Street, 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 9411, 66 Grand Street, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Job: 7626, 75-87 Grand Street, 1960-1990; cuid39089 (Box 17, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 7722, 78 Grand Street, 1970-1981; cuid39098 (Box 23, Folder 10, Box 28, Folder 1, Flat-file-folder 12, Flat-file-folder 14)
  - Job: 8926, 107 Grand Street, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Job: 7840, 134-140 Grand Street, 1960-1982; cuid39093 (Box 16, Folder 4, Box 23, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 9016, 140 Grand Street, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Job: 7718, 163 Grand Street, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Job: 7861, 39 Great Jones Street, 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 7307, 16-18 Greene Street, 1973-1976; cuid39135 (Box 15, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 7424, 53 Greene Street, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Job: 7730, 62 Greene Street, 1979-1981 (Box 29, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 9530 A, 65-67 Greene Street, 1995-2000 (Flat-file-folder 15)
  - Job: 7403, 70 Greene Street, 1969-1974 (Box 29, Folder 25, Flat-file-folder 12)
  - Job: 8228, 93-99 Greene Street, 1983-1986; cuid39087 (Box 1, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 4, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 18, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Job: 7828, 131 Greene Street, 1978-1981 (Box 35, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 7859, 135 Greene Street, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 6, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 7819, 136 Greene Street, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Job: 7860, 137 Greene Street, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Job: 7709, 142-144 Greene Street, 1977-1981; cuid39144 (Box 27, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 9, Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Job: 7114 A, 148 Greene Street, 1971; cuid39133 (Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 7807, 148 Greene Street, 1978; cuid39131 (Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 9223, 317-319 Greenwich Street, 1990-1993 (Box 23, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 9809, 321A Greenwich Street, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 7, Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Job: 7831, 335 Greenwich Street, 1978-1980 (Box 35, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 12, Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Job: 7636, 407-411 Greenwich Street, 1977-1980, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 10, Box 29, Folder 19, Flat-file-folder 10)
  - Job: 7756, 413 Greenwich Street, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 2, Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Job: 7428 / 7429 / 7738, 424 Greenwich Street, 1973-1984; cuid41091 (Box 9, Folder 1-2, Flat-file-folder 12, Box 28, Folder 11, Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 13, Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Job: 7776, 533 Greenwich Street, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Job: 8018, 627 Greenwich Street, undated; cuid39130 (Flat-file-folder 18, Flat-file-folder 3, Box 38, Folder 5-7)
  - Job: 8224, 627 Greenwich Street, 1983-1987 (Flat-file-folder 17, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 10, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 11)
  - Job: 8425, 627 Greenwich Street, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 4-5, Flat-file-folder 16)
  - Job: 7854, 363-67 Greenwich Street, 1978-1981; cuid39083 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Job: 7847, 644 Greenwich Street, 1978; cuid40890 (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Job: 7423, 719 Greenwich Street, 1974-1983; cuid40879 (Box 8, Folder 10, Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Job: 9205, 719 Greenwich Street, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 3, Flat-file-folder 13)
  - Job: 7933, 759 Greenwich Street, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 8, Flat-file-folder 10)